websitevalue.co.uk 2015-05-16

# Web Site Value Calculator and Website Valuation Tool

We know that you care how your information is used, and we appreciate your trust that we will use it carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting us, you are accepting the privacy policy described below.

**1.Introduction and general terms**  
Websitevalue.co.uk is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy, which is a binding part of Websitevalue.co.uk's Terms of Use, explains the type of information Websitevalue.co.uk collects through its website and what Websitevalue.co.uk does with it. 

**2.What types of information will Websitevalue.co.uk collect?** If you are visiting the Websitevalue.co.uk website (Websitevalue.co.uk), we collect the following information: the full Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the Web page, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, which may include a domain name; the date and time for each page you view. 

This information allows us to provide you with information about the Web page you are viewing and to estimate as to how much a website is worth. Thus, for every Web page you view while using the Websitevalue.co.uk 

**3.Does Websitevalue.co.uk collect personally identifiable information?**  
Sometimes the URLs we collect through websitevalue.co.uk contains personal information about you. For example, when you enter information on a Web page (e.g., when you complete an online registration form or sign up for a contest), the operator of the website may insert that information into its URL for that or the next page. This information often appears after a question mark ("?") in the URL, although it can appear in other places. This means that your name, your address, your e-mail address, or similar information you might consider private or personally identifiable which you enter into a Web page sometimes becomes part of a URL that is then transmitted to Websitevalue.co.uk and automatically stored in Websitevalue.co.uk's databases. 

If you e-mail Websitevalue.co.uk, we may store copies of such e-mail or similar communications between you and Websitevalue.co.uk. This can result in the collection of your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information you may have in your e-mail text, addresses, or other fields, as well as the collection of the your IP address, the Internet or other routing of your communication, and the date and time of your communication. 

All transmissions between you and Websitevalue.co.uk, including e-mails, URLs, usage paths, and any personally identifiable information they might contain, pass through many third party machines, operating systems, programs, browsers, Web servers, networks, routers, Ethernet switches, ISPs, proxy servers, intranets, the public telephone systems, or other devices, any of which may create activity logs containing such transmissions. 

**4.How Websitevalue.co.uk uses the information it collects?**  
We do not disclose your e-mail address to business partners or to anyone other than employees and agents working for or on behalf of Websitevalue.co.uk, except as required by subpoenas, court orders, or legal requirements. 

We use IP addresses to diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our website. Your IP address also is used by Websitevalue.co.uk to gather broad demographic information, such as your general geographic location and Internet Service Provider. IP addresses are further used to help determine the number of Websitevalue.co.uk users. This demographic information may also be used by Websitevalue.co.uk to analyze aggregate Web usage behavior. 

We use Web usage paths to estimate website values. 

**5.Will Websitevalue.co.uk share the personal information with anyone else?**  
Your privacy is of core value to Websitevalue.co.uk. Except as described below, Websitevalue.co.uk does not disclose personally identifying information collected from any user to any third party. 

We disclose any information we possess in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal requirements, and such information might be used by the receiving party to determine your identity, your Web usage and online shopping behavior, or other things about you. We generally do not inform users of such requests for information, although we might try to do so in some cases. 

In the event that Websitevalue.co.uk or substantially all of its assets are sold or acquired, all information collected by Websitevalue.co.uk would be transferred to the acquiring party. In any such transfer, however, such information would remain subject to any applicable terms and conditions, including the terms of this Privacy Policy and any amendment thereto. 

**6.How is your information protected?**  
Websitevalue.co.uk collects certain personally identifiable information provided by you. Your usage paths and other information provided by you can be accessed only by a limited number of Websitevalue.co.uk employees. Websitevalue.co.uk prohibits its employees from using any of this information to determine your identity. 

**7.How to Change Your Information?**   
Websitevalue.co.uk also enable users to delete information, including usage path, shopping, and demographic information. 

**8.Changes to Websitevalue.co.uk's Privacy Policy**   
This privacy policy may be updated from time to time so you agree to check it each time you submit personal information to any Websitevalue.co.uk's website. The date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page. 

**9.Contacting Websitevalue.co.uk about this Privacy Policy**   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy then please Contact us at: 1st Floor, Torrington House 111 Hare Lane Claygate, KT10 0QY, United Kingdom
